American Federation of Labor Records, Part 2 on Microfilm 5760 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- State Federations of Labor Correspondence, 1935-1945 (Reel 30)
  - 0583. Box 36/Folder 1. Texas. 7 pages., 1937-1939; 21 (Reel 30)
  - 0590. Box 36/Folder 1. Utah. 78 pages., 1935-1941; 22 (Reel 30)
  - 0668. Box 36/Folder 1. Vermont. 3 pages., 1936; 23 (Reel 30)
  - 0671. Box 36/Folder 1. Virginia. 17 pages., 1936-1942; 24 (Reel 30)
    1936-1937 and 1942.
  - 0688. Box 36/Folder 1. Washington. 15 pages., 1937-1939; 25 (Reel 30)
  - 0703. Box 36/Folder 2. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. West Virginia. 255 pages., 1936-1942; 26 (Reel 30)
  - 0959. Box 36/Folder 3. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. "W" (continued), 27 (Reel 30)
  - 0960. Box 36/Folder 3. Wisconsin. 30 pages., 1936-1937; 28 (Reel 30)
  - 0990. Box 36/Folder 3. Wyoming. 26 pages., 1937-1939; 29 (Reel 30)
- Central Labor Union Correspondence, 1935-1950. (Reel 31)
  - 0001. Box 37/Folder 1. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "A", 1 (Reel 31)
  - 0002. Box 37/Folder 1. Alabama. 78 pages., 1935-1938; 2 (Reel 31)
  - 0080. Box 37/Folder 1. Alaska. 5 pages., 1938-1947; 3 (Reel 31)
    1938 and 1947
  - 0085. Box 37/Folder 1. Arizona. 8 pages., 1936-1946; 4 (Reel 31)
    1936-1938 and 1946
  - 0093. Box 37/Folder 1. Arkansas. 64 pages., 1936-1939; 5 (Reel 31)
  - 0157. Box 37/Folder 2. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. California. 142 pages., 1935-1937; 6 (Reel 31)
    1935-June 1937
  - 0330. Box 37/Folder 3. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. California. 171 pages., 1937; 7 (Reel 31)
    July-December 1937
  - 0502. Box 37/Folder 4. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. California. 157 pages., 1938; 8 (Reel 31)
  - 0659. Box 37/Folder 5. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. California. 140 pages., 1939-1947; 9 (Reel 31)
  - 0799. Box 38/Folder 1. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Canada. 206 pages., 1936-1946; 10 (Reel 31)
- Central Labor Union Correspondence, 1935-1950 (Reel 32)
  - 0001. Box 38/Folder 2. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "C" (continued)-"H", 1 (Reel 32)
  - 0002. Box 38/Folder 2. Connecticut. 17 pages., 1937-1944; 2 (Reel 32)
  - 0019. Box 38/Folder 2. Florida. 69 pages., 1937-1939; 3 (Reel 32)
  - 0088. Box 38/Folder 2. Georgia. 38 pages., 1936-1944; 4 (Reel 32)
    1936-1938 and 1944
  - 0126. Box 38/Folder 2. Hawaii. 3 pages., 1943; 5 (Reel 32)
  - 0129. Box 38/Folder 3. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Illinois. 224 pages., 1936-1940; 6 (Reel 32)
  - 0353. Box 38/Folder 4. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Indiana. 271 pages., 1936-1944; 7 (Reel 32)
  - 0624. Box 38/Folder 5. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "I" (continued)-"L", 8 (Reel 32)
  - 0625. Box 38/Folder 5. Iowa. 131 pages., 1936-1947; 9 (Reel 32)
    1936-1941, 1944, and 1947
  - 0756. Box 38/Folder 5. Kansas. 16 pages., 1935-1944; 10 (Reel 32)
    1935-1940 and 1944
  - 0772. Box 38/Folder 5. Kentucky. 17 pages., 1936-1943; 11 (Reel 32)
  - 0789. Box 38/Folder 5. Louisiana. 38 pages., 1936-1941; 12 (Reel 32)
    1936 and 1941
  - 0827. Box 39/Folder 1. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "M", 13 (Reel 32)
  - 0828. Box 39/Folder 1. Maryland. 21 pages., 1936-1947; 14 (Reel 32)
    1936-1937, 1942, and 1947.
  - 0849. Box 39/Folder 1. Massachusetts. 19 pages., 1936-1944; 15 (Reel 32)
  - 0868. Box 39/Folder 1. Michigan. 144 pages., 1937-1950; 16 (Reel 32)
- Central Labor Union Correspondence, 1935-1950 (Reel 33)
  - 0001. Box 39/Folder 2. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Minnesota. 196 pages., 1936-1941; 1 (Reel 33)
    1936-June 1941
  - 0198. Box 39/Folder 3. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Minnesota. 213 pages., 1941-1947; 2 (Reel 33)
    July 1941- 1947
  - 0411. Box 39/Folder 4. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "M" (continued)-"N", 3 (Reel 33)
  - 0412. Box 39/Folder 4. Missouri. 20 pages., 1935-1945; 4 (Reel 33)
    1935-1938 and 1945
  - 0432. Box 39/Folder 4. Montana. 100 pages., 1937-1947; 5 (Reel 33)
    1937-1942 and 1947
  - 0532. Box 39/Folder 4. Nebraska. 68 pages., 1939-1944; 6 (Reel 33)
    1939 and 1943-1944
  - 0600. Box 39/Folder 1. Nevada. 7 pages., 1943; 7 (Reel 33)
  - 0607. Box 39/Folder 4. New Hampshire. 4 pages., 1937; 8 (Reel 33)
  - 0611. Box 39/Folder 4. New Jersey. 52 pages., 1936-1946; 9 (Reel 33)
    1936-1941 and 1946
  - 0663. Box 39/Folder 5. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. New York. 122 pages., 1936-1950; 10 (Reel 33)
    1936-1944, 1949-1950.
  - 0785. Box 40/Folder 1. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "N" (continued)-"O", 11 (Reel 33)
  - 0786. Box 40/Folder 1. North Carolina. 13 pages., 1941-1947; 12 (Reel 33)
    1941-1942 and 1947
  - 0799. Box 40/Folder 1. Ohio. 100 pages., 1935-1937; 13 (Reel 33)
    1935-March 1937
- Central Labor Union Correspondence, 1935-1950 (Reel 34)
  - 0001. Box 40/Folder 1. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Ohio. 190 pages., 1937; 1 (Reel 34)
  - 0191. Box 40/Folder 2. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Ohio. 182 pages., 1938-1950; 2 (Reel 34)
  - 0373. Box 40/Folder 3. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "O" (continued), 3 (Reel 34)
  - 0374. Box 40/Folder 3. Oklahoma. 14 pages., 1937-1942; 4 (Reel 34)
    1937, 1939, and 1942
  - 0388. Box 40/Folder 3. Oregon. 53 pages., 1937; 5 (Reel 34)
  - 0441. Box 40/Folder 3. Oklahoma. 6 pages., 1938-1939; 6 (Reel 34)
  - 0447. Box 40/Folder 3. Oregon. 24 pages., 1939-1944; 7 (Reel 34)
  - 0471. Box 40/Folder 4. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Pennsylvania. 217 pages., 1935-1945; 8 (Reel 34)
  - 0689. Box 40/Folder 5. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. "R"-"V", 9 (Reel 34)
  - 0690. Box 40/Folder 5. Rhode Island. 9 pages., 1937; 10 (Reel 34)
  - 0699. Box 40/Folder 5. South Carolina. 3 pages., 1935; 11 (Reel 34)
  - 0702. Box 40/Folder 5. South Dakota. 7 pages., 1938-1943; 12 (Reel 34)
    1938 and 1943
  - 0709. Box 40/Folder 5. Tennessee. 17 pages., 1937; 13 (Reel 34)
  - 0726. Box 40/Folder 5. Texas. 1 page., 1938; 14 (Reel 34)
  - 0727. Box 40/Folder 5. Tennessee. 19 pages., 1938-1947; 15 (Reel 34)
    1938, 1942, and 1947
  - 0746. Box 40/Folder 5. Texas. 61 pages., 1935-1944; 16 (Reel 34)
  - 0807. Box 40/Folder 5. Utah. 18 pages., 1937-1938; 17 (Reel 34)
  - 0825. Box 40/Folder 5. Virginia. 47 pages., 1937-1947; 18 (Reel 34)
    1937 and 1944-1947
- Central Labor Union Correspondence, 1935-1950. Local Union Correspondence, 1937-1947. (Reel 35)
  - 0001. Box 41/Folder 1. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Washington. 262 pages., 1936-1947; 1 (Reel 35)
    1936-1942 and 1947
  - 0264. Box 41/Folder 2. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. West Virginia. 107 pages., 1936-1947; 2 (Reel 35)
    1936-1938 and 1944-1947
  - 0371. Box 41/Folder 3. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. 188 pages. Wisconsin., 1936-1938; 3 (Reel 35)
    1936-February 1938
  - 0559. Box 41/Folder 4. Correspondence of Central Labor Unions. Wisconsin. 41 pages., 1938-1943; 4 (Reel 35)
    March 1938- 1943
  - 0630. Box 42/Folder 1. Correspondence of Local Unions. Aluminum Workers. 142 pages., 1937-1944; 5 (Reel 35)
- Local Union Correspondence, 1937-1947. Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1936-1950. (Reel 36)
  - 0001. Box 41/Folder 2. Correspondence of Local Unions. "B"-"E", 1 (Reel 36)
  - 0002. Box 41/Folder 2. Barbers. 3 pages., 1937; 2 (Reel 36)
  - 0005. Box 41/Folder 2. Bookbinders. 3 pages., 1937-1938; 3 (Reel 36)
  - 0008. Box 41/Folder 2. Boot and Shoe Workers. 9 pages., 1937-1938; 4 (Reel 36)
  - 0017. Box 41/Folder 2. Building Service Workers. 4 pages., 1937; 5 (Reel 36)
  - 0021. Box 41/Folder 2. Building Laborers and Carpenters. 23 pages., 1937-1939; 6 (Reel 36)
  - 0044. Box 41/Folder 2. Button Workers. 4 pages., 1938; 7 (Reel 36)
  - 0048. Box 41/Folder 2. Cannery Workers. 17 pages., 1939-1945; 8 (Reel 36)
    1939 and 1945
  - 0065. Box 41/Folder 2. Cement Workers. 4 pages., 1937-1938; 9 (Reel 36)
  - 0069. Box 41/Folder 2. Chemical Workers. 13 pages., 1938; 10 (Reel 36)
  - 0082. Box 41/Folder 2. Clothing Workers. 3 pages., 1937; 11 (Reel 36)
  - 0085. Box 41/Folder 2. Electrical Workers. 5 pages., 1937-1938; 12 (Reel 36)
  - 0090. Box 42/Folder 3. Correspondence of Local Unions. "F"-"T", 13 (Reel 36)
  - 0091. Box 42/Folder 3. Farm Equipment and Metal Workers. 6 pages., 1945; 14 (Reel 36)
  - 0097. Box 42/Folder 3. Filling Station Workers. 3 pages., 1937; 15 (Reel 36)
  - 0100. Box 42/Folder 3. Fishermen. 4 pages., 1939; 16 (Reel 36)
  - 0104. Box 42/Folder 3. Furniture Workers. 9 pages., 1940; 17 (Reel 36)
  - 0113. Box 42/Folder 3. Grain Processors. 11 pages., 1939-1947; 18 (Reel 36)
    1939, 1945, and 1947
  - 0124. Box 42/Folder 3. Longshoremen. 5 pages., 1939; 19 (Reel 36)
  - 0129. Box 42/Folder 3. Operating Engineers. 4 pages., 1937; 20 (Reel 36)
  - 0133. Box 42/Folder 3. Optical Workers. 3 pages., 1947; 21 (Reel 36)
  - 0136. Box 42/Folder 3. Railway Carmen. 5 pages., 1938; 22 (Reel 36)
  - 0141. Box 42/Folder 3. State, County, and Municipal Employees. 6 pages., 1937; 23 (Reel 36)
  - 0147. Box 42/Folder 3. Sugar Refinery Workers. 9 pages., 1938; 24 (Reel 36)
  - 0156. Box 42/Folder 3. Teachers. 32 pages., 1937-1938; 25 (Reel 36)
  - 0188. Box 42/Folder 4. Correspondence of Local Unions. Stenographers and Bookkeepers. 107 pages., 1937-1939; 26 (Reel 36)
  - 0295. Box 42/Folder 5. Correspondence of Local Unions. "T" (continued)-"U", 27 (Reel 36)
  - 0296. Box 42/Folder 5. Textile Workers. 6 pages., 1937-1938; 28 (Reel 36)
  - 0302. Box 42/Folder 5. Theatrical Workers. 4 pages., 1943; 29 (Reel 36)
  - 0306. Box 42/Folder 5. Typographical Union. 43 pages., 1937-1938; 30 (Reel 36)
  - 0349. Box 42/Folder 5. Utility Workers. 4 pages., 1942; 31 (Reel 36)
  - 0353. Box 43/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers Favoring the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 40 pages., 1936-1937; 32 (Reel 36)
  - 0393. Box 42/Folder 2. Pledges of Loyalty to the American Federation of Labor. 203 pages., 1936-1937; 33 (Reel 36)
    1936-April 1937
  - 0596. Box 43/Folder 3. Pledges of Loyalty to the American Federation of Labor. 109 pages., 1937; 34 (Reel 36)
    May-September 1937
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1936-1950 (Reel 37)
  - 0001. Box 43/Folder 3 (continued). Pledges of Loyalty to the American Federation of Labor. 98 pages., 1937; 1 (Reel 37)
  - 0099. Box 43/Folder 4. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 181 pages., 1936-1937; 2 (Reel 37)
    1936-June 1937
  - 0280. Box 43/Folder 5. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 181 pages., 1937; 3 (Reel 37)
  - 0461. Box 44/Folder 1. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 155 pages., 1938; 4 (Reel 37)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1936-1950. (Reel 38)
  - 0001. Box 44/Folder 2. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 191 pages., 1939; 1 (Reel 38)
    January-June 1939
  - 0192. Box 44/Folder 3. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 116 pages., 1939; 2 (Reel 38)
    July-December 1939
  - 0308/ Box 44/Folder 4. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 167 pages., 1940; 3 (Reel 38)
  - 0475. Box 44/Folder 5. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 92 pages., 1941-1944; 4 (Reel 38)
  - 0567. Box 44/Folder 6. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 142 pages., 1945-1950; 5 (Reel 38)
    1945-1947 and 1950